Coming this fall...
Some cops can read minds.
Did you do it or not?
I'm not a mind reader.
Some cops can see the past.
I could solve this crime if only
I had personally watched it happen.
And some cops get help from angels.
Come on, Gabriel,
you must have seen something!
Nah, man, I ain't seen nothing for no cop.
But there's still one cop
with no special abilitieswhatsoever.
Ah, there's only one way to know
who committed this crime.
I'll just have to find out.
Detective Klaus Mandela is
the Finder Outer.
This truly is
the golden age of television.
Hey, Papa, want to help me
earn a merit badge?
Hmm? Sorry, son.
Right now,
NBC needs my love more than you do.
Lrrr!
Either help the boy,
or go outside and degauss the lawn!
Oh, very well.
Merit badges.
Ah, this brings me back.
Oh, Bone Whittling.
I used to love that.
Patricide.
Well, let's work up to that one.
How about Skull Arranging?
That is for Grrrl Scouts!
Men bring the skulls home,
women arrange them.
I'm gonna help you earn a manly badge.
Planetary Invasion!
But that's really hard.
Hard shmard.
I'll let you invade the easiest planet
in the whole galaxy.
Good news, everyone!
I'm in terrible pain.
- How is that good news?
- It's not.
I've run out of Good News brand
herbal supplement.
If you don't get me
more Good News, everyone,
my arthritis will make me seize up
like a dried monkey carcass.
I've seen those.
In the Great Monkey Desert.
We interrupt your TV being off
for this special bulletin.
An alien saucer has been detected
en route to Earth.
We now go live to the White House lawn,
where such things usually land.
Go on. Ring the bell and invade them.
Yes?
Um, hi?
I... I'm Jrrr,
of the planet Omicron Persei 8.
Uh, what's that? Speak up, son.
Don't look at me. You're invading him.
I just wanted to know...
Well, I'm here to invade your planet?
Oh, what a cute little...
Uh-oh.
Brannigan! Get out here and surrender
before I get my expletives deleted!
And Earth is yours.
So, sire, how may I please you?
Go ahead.
His bowels aren't gonna disem themselves.
Can't we just go?
Mmm-mmm. Not until you blow something up.
Aw, man.
Uh, uh...
Just pick something and blow it up
so I can get home in time
for The Finder Outer.
Oh...
What the...
All right, good enough. Let's go.
He killed my second-to-last Agnew.
Rose Mary! Sweep the booze bottles
off my desk!
I'm addressing the planet.
First, brush your teeth!
Yeah, yeah.
My fellow Earthicans,
a great American monster
has been silenced.
Clone of Agnew is gone,
killed in his clubbing shoes
by ruthless Omicronians.
But we're gonna get even, by golly.
Aw, crap, he's on every channel!
Effective immediately,
I'm calling fora planetary embargo
against Omicron Persei 8.
Where's my Hot in Cleveland?
All trade with the Omicronians
stops today.
And that includes cultural exports.
Cultural?
I'm talking about TV!
Nixon out!
No!
Well, I never liked going
to Omicron Persei 8 anyway.
If we want to breathe sulfuric acid
and get our heads torn off
by giant lizards,
we can always go to Gary, Indiana.
Even I would never send you
to Gary, Indiana.
But I am sending you to Omicron Persei 8.
Oh, my gosh, are you kidding?
You see, the active ingredient
in my Good News herbal supplement
grows only on Omicron Persei 8.
And due to the embargo,
the only place to get it
is straight from the source.
The deadly, deadly source.
I will not endanger this crew
for some quack remedy.
Ha! The Sacred Weed of Omicron
is a serious herb.
Sacred Weed you say?
Sweet toke of Ocracoke,
this stuff's the Omichronic!
To the ship!
We can't get through.
The planet's blockaded.
That won't stop us.
Activate cloaking device.
There's no such thing.
Then, engage deflector shields.
That's from TV, Geordi.
Well, what sort of stealth technology
do we have?
A can of paint.
Sir, there's an Omicronian ship
requesting safe passage home.
Home, eh? That's where I live.
Let them through the blockade.
Okay, buddy up
and look out for Omicronians.
It's up to everyone
to get their partner back alive.
Fry, you go with Bender.
Amy, with Leela.
And I'll go with...
Screwed again, my friend.
Hey, Bender, you better check your ass.
I think it's leaking enchantment.
That's not enchantment, it's the herbs!
Bender's electric field
is activating their bioluminescence.
Whoa!
We'll need scientific samples.
Everyone, start filling these dime bags.
Whoa, a palace!
Parapets, battlements,
everything my
Big Book of Castles promised.
I'm gonna sneak a closer look.
Bender, you'll let me know
if we have to cheese it, right?
First Law of Robotics, baby.
Five-O, five-O!
Five what?
Five Omicronians!
Everyone, grab your buddy
and get back to the ship!
Coming through!
Is everyone on board?
I got my buddy.
Hermes is my buddy.
Bender, where's Fry?
I saw him in the, uh, kitchen.
With Dinah.
You know,
the dyno-matic food-service robot.
Let's go already!
I smell the stink of Earth humans.
Fan out!
They got away, Your Scaliness.
We must have just missed them.
The ground is still warm.
I want my Earth shows!
These local programs
are completely unwatchable.
Hey, Pops, want to play skull ball?
I'm watching something here.
Hello?
Ow!
Uh, y... you can come out.
Don't be s... scared.
Mmm.
You're an alien?
Do you speak English?
English?
You must be a terrestrial
from that Earth ship they were hunting.
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
Hey, thanks.
You want some candy?
Ew. You were eating my turds?
Feces pieces?
Blech!
You must be hungry.
Really hungry.
Come inside, I'll feed you.
Okay, but I'm kind of picky.
I'm gonna call you "T."
For terrestrial?
No, "Turd-eater."
But I have to hide you from my dad.
He's really mad at humans
'cause he can't
watch television.
Your dad must be Lrrr!
"Ruler of the planet
Omicron Persei 8."
He's a terrible father.
Bender, do you know where Fry is?
I haven't seen him since we got back
from Omicron Persei 8.
Fry? Uh, you just missed him.
He went out to buy you flowers.
Whatever kind you like best.
'Cause he loves you and crap.
Aw, that's so sweet.
Thanks, Bender.
Dude!
That herb you scored cleared up
my arthritis and my glaucoma.
Have you seen Fry?
Fry? Uh, he, uh, went to get you a burrito
at the gas station.
Awesome.
You got to love a dude
that brings the munchie.
Fry is one guy
I'd definitely never abandon.
This is my fleam.
You use it to peel the skin
off your enemies
layer by layer till they die or whatever.
Neat! Hey, you know
who would love fleaming stuff?
My friend Bender,
who I'll never see again.
Aw, you're homesick, aren't you, T.?
Mmm-hmm. I miss Earth,
and I'm still hungry.
Do you have any more of that candy?
No, but I have a toy Earth.
Home.
I didn't abandon you! You wandered off!
Stop judging me, Fry-bed!
Oh, it's just not the same
without the muffled screams.
If only I could hear your voice again.
Hello, it's me, Fry!
I'm not here right now,
'cause we're out getting drunk
at the Olive Garden.
So just leave a message for myself
or Benderafter the tone.See you!
Aw!
Fry? Are you home?
We're supposed to have a date
at the adults-only pancake house.
Of course he's here
and not on another planet!
Ooh! In fact,
he's about to talk to you right now.
Oh, good.
Hello, it's me, Fry.
I'm... drunk... right now.
So just leave.
Okay... I love you.
Olive... you.
And finally,
our new employee of the month is Fry.
He's really been putting
his nose to the grindstone,
according to Bender's constant updates.
He's been working so hard,
we barely even see him.
It's strange, that.
There's nothing strange about it.
He's just out of sight
around this corner, exterminating mice.
Mice... Mice...
Myself... Elf...
- Elf.
- Oops.
Elves are back.
T. text home?
Sorry, boy.
'Cause of the embargo,
our planets aren't allowed to communicate.
Update Facebook status home?
Look, my scout manual has a section
on emergency communication.
Maybe we can rig something up.
Would you like that, boy?
Huh? Would you, boy?
Watch out!
Whoa!
Sorry. This planet has moon problem.
So what makes this thing fly?
It's powered by love.
Aw!
Okay, stop loving me so much
so we can land.
No problem.
Okay, this tech dump has every kind of
high-tech communications device.
Using all of them,
I'm sure I can get a message home.
There. Finished.
Oh, God, I can't believe I abandoned Fry.
I'll never forget the feel of
his soft skin against my flailing fists.
Oh, wait, there's still some beer left.
Huh?
"S.O.S."?
Those are the letters that Fry knows!
He's alive!
Yeah?
Jrrr, how do I watch a funny
on the YouTube?
It's my dad. Quick, hide!
What's going on in here?
Uh, nothing.
I was just playing foosball. By myself.
I thought I told you to kill those foos.
Hmm.
Let's just have a look
in the toy closet, shall we?
Skull, skull, skull,
skull, skull... Wait.
Why haven't you fleamed this skull?
Hi, Mr. Lrrr.
Hey, you're one of those Earth spies
from that Earth ship, aren't you?
Are you going to kill me?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Jrrr is.
Three, two, one...
Hang on, Fry, I'm a-comin' to save you!
You are... my... here... o.
Shut up, Fry, I know it.
It's a nice day.
We'll take him out to the yard,
and after you shoot him,
we'll play catch with his bladder.
But I can't. He's my pet.
You shot your hamster.
I told you, that was suicide.
He looks kind of sick.
What have you been feeding him?
Uh, some stuff I made.
Whatever. It's time
I made a man out of you.
Right here, today,
while I'm not missing anything good on TV.
Now get in there
and shoot your beloved pet!
I guess this is good-bye.
It's okay, Jrrr.
The week I spent hiding in your closet,
eating your turds,
was the best week of my life.
Aah!
Run, boy! Run!
He's escaping on a bicycle
powered by love.
Which is an ordinary thing on this planet.
They're getting away. Love harder!
We can't, sir.
The men have been hurt too often.
We did it! We're home free!
Yes, but...
I'm dying.
Not 'cause of the turds.
Can I have a turd?
Just rest.
I'm gonna get you to a vet.
I am Drrr,
doctor of the planet Omicron Persei 8.
It appears you may have ingested
something toxic.
Open your mouth and say "Ah!"
- Ah...
- Good God!
Here, take some of this herb
to ease the pain.
Can you save him?
I could, but he'd only live
another 80 years at most.
The humane thing is to put him to sleep.
Oh!
Stop! I won't let you do it!
Dad?
Because you have to do it.
Be a man for once
and fleam this wretched creature.
I won't.
I'm not exactly like you, okay?
I don't want to conquer planets
or kill things,
or wear a lame cape.
It's not lame, it's lamé.
And this thing lying on the bed?
He may be a weird skin ball full of love
and some kind of red juice,
which is delicious, by the way,
I've been drinking it every day,
but we're friends.
And I will not kill him.
You know,
standing up to me is pretty manly.
I'll tell you what, sport.
I'll kill him for you.
Good news!
Nobody has to kill him after all.
Because he already died!
T.!
Son...
I didn't mean it about the cape.
Capes are cool!
He's alive.
At least his butt is.
Fry?
Bender.
I knew you wouldn't abandon me
for much more than a week.
What's happening? Why is his butt glowing?
The electromagnetic intensity
of the robot's friendship
is causing the herbs in his bowels
to bioluminesce with love.
- Probably.
- That's right, ugly.
I'm here to take my friend home.
Whoa, is that a fleam?
But, T., can't you stay with me?
We could grow up together.
No. I need to grow up on my own planet.
I must bid you farewell,
my special friend.
What the hell's been going on around here?
Ah, Fry!
You've been working so hard,
we haven't seen you in days.
Wait, what?
No, I was stuck on... Ow!
Uh, stuck on another delivery
that he undertook on his own.
We're all very lucky
and not suspicious to have him.
Hey, Fry, things sure have been
going great between us.
Remember that make out session
in that dark closet?
You were like a machine.
But I...
Olive... you.
It's me, Fry!
It sure is.